景色真美
This spot is beautiful.
嗯 的确是
Yeah, it really is.
你们真幸运 我小时候可不是在这么美的地方长大的
You guys are lucky. I didn't have a place like this where I grew up.
你在说什么？你小时候居住的地方离这里只有半小时的路程
What are you talking about? You grew up like half an hour from here.
随便你们怎么说 我父母不常让我出去
Whatever. My parents didn't let me out much.
对我们来说这里是个神奇的地方
Yeah, well, it was really amazing for us.
高中时我们经常翘课来这里
In high school we used to sneak out and come here all the time.
是的 三更半夜出去约会 实际上
That's right. Late-night rendezvous. In fact,
我们在这个特别的 地方第一次分享了龙舌兰酒
we shared our first bottle of tequila right here at this very spot.
哇 真高兴你还记得
Wow. I am impressed that you even remember that.
真高兴你还记得
"I am impressed that you even remember that."
你们觉得自己现在还是和从前一样吗？
So do you guys feel like you were the same as you were back then?
我知道我是没变
Well, I know I'm exactly the same.
长大后我依然对未来不知所措
I still have absolutely no idea what I want to do when I grow up.
嗯 你曾经在Foot Locker公司工作过 如果你回去的话
Well, hey, you used to work at Foot Locker, and I'm sure
我保证他们还会用你的
if you went back and asked, they'd give you the job.
- 真搞笑 - 你呢 尼克？
- Very funny. - What about you, Nick?
- 你变了吗？- 嗯
- Have you changed much? - Mmm-mm.
我必须坦白 特雷弗越来越帅了
Although I must say, Trevor has gotten way hotter.
这是实话 我的朋友 对吗？
You know that that is a fact, my friend, okay?
我的下巴现在变宽了 这很明显
My jaw is way wider now. It's striking.
好了 大帅哥 你和我
All right, loverboy. How about you and me
去取些木材生火 怎么样？
go get some wood for this fire, huh?
好的 小心些
All right, take care.
我预感下几个月会有好运
I got a really good feeling about the next couple of months.
是吗？为什么？
Yeah? Why is that?
如果我们关闭了自己的几个账户
If we just close a couple of our own accounts,
你清楚那对咱们来说是多大的财富
you know how huge that could be for us?
嗯 我的意思是 提前退休很好
Yeah, I mean, retiring early would be very nice.
30就退休？
By 30?
哦 靠看 看
Oh, shit. Look, look.
真恶心
Gross, dude.
过来 你连一个小螃蟹雷都害怕？
Come here. What, you afraid of a little crab?
真恶心 这东西真的令人作呕 别
Gross, dude! Those things are just sick! Don't!
- 来呀 - 不 别这样 别闹了
- Come on. Come on. - No, don't! Dude, don't! Don't!
恶心的东西
Fucking pussy.
这太令人激动了
This is so exciting!
是的 也许我应该等到明天再告诉他
Yeah. Maybe I should wait till tomorrow.
不 你得今天告诉他
No, you have to tell him tonight.
嘿 你们去了很久
Hey. Took you guys long enough.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
就这样 就这样了 好吗 准备好了吗？
There it goes. There it goes. Okay, ready?
很好 我准备好了
Nice. Yeah, I'm ready.
- 生日快乐  - 哦
- Happy birthday! - Oh!
- 哦 蜡烛灭了 重点 - 等等
- Oh, they went out. Relight. - Wait wait.
- 好了 - 现在许个愿
- All right. - Okay, now make a wish.
我说不出来 一切都很完美
I can't. Everything's perfect.
- 总有不完美的吧 - 噢 亲爱的
- That's lame. - Oh. Oh, sweetie.
随便了
Whatever, dude.
如果你需要的话 我能说出很多愿望
If you need something, I've got a whole list of things.
- 一百万美元怎么样？- 已经点好了
- How about a million dollars? - Blow 'em out, already.
- 来吧 - 好吧 好吧
- Let's do this. - All right, all right!
- 哈 - 不
- Yay! - No!
- 快点 不 那是我买的 - 这是我的生日蛋糕
- Come on. No. I bought 'em. - It's my birthday cake.
- 我想拍张照 - 什么照？
- I want it in the shot. - In what shot?
- 好主意 - 正经点
- Good idea, okay. - Behave.
- 好了 大家注意了 - 来 快点 我想要一个纸杯蛋糕
- Okay, everybody. - Come on, hurry up, I want a cupcake.
我知道 先忍着点儿 好吗？
I know, just hold your horses for a minute, all right?
- 真是艺术品 太完美了 - 像贫民区的奶油
- Art. It's perfection. - It's kinda ghetto frosting.
- 味道很好 - 我最喜欢这种了
- That's good though. - That's my favorite.
你们准备好了吗？
Yup. Are you ready?
是的
Yes.
- 大家说"茄子" - 茄子
- Everybody say "chingas." - Chingas.
- 好了 - 茄子
- Good, guys. - Chingas.
来看看 女士们先生们
Check it out, ladies and gentlemen.
我为自己买了特殊的生日蜡烛
I brought my own special kind of birthday candle.
- 好的 - 药
- All right. - Drugs!
- 你们两个留下来好好玩吧 - 太好了
- You kids have fun. - That is awesome.
- 点燃一下 - 过来
- Light it up. - Come here.
- 嘿 你去哪？- 到处走走
- Hey, where are you going? - Somewhere.
- 真的吗？- 和你一起
- Really? - With you.
- 好的 - 相机给我
- Okay. - Camera, please.
- 是的 长官 - 穿上外衣
- Yes, sir. - Put this on.
- 好的 - 这真令人激动
- All right. - This is kind of exciting.
- 我现在要蒙上你的眼睛 - 真的吗？
- Oh, I will now be blindfolding you. - Really?
- 你要占我便宜吗？- 我也许会的
- Are you going to take advantage of me? - Mm, I might.
- 好的 拿着 - 嗯
- All right, hold this. - Okay.
- 然后… - 哦
- And... - Oh!
- 我们一会儿就回来 - 一会见
- We shall return. - See you later.
别担心我
Don't worry about me.
- 打开 - 哦
- Open. - Oh.
记得我们第一次来这儿吗？
Remember the first time we came here?
是的 那时什么时候了 好像是三年前？
Yeah. What was that, like three years ago?
是的
Yeah.
尼克 有些事
Nick, um, there's something
我想告诉你
that I want to tell you.
我先说
Me first.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
尼克 哦
Nick! Oh!
- 真漂亮 - 但愿它是颗钻石 但…
- It's beautiful. - Wish it was a diamond, but...
嗯 我很喜欢它 我爱你
Well, I love it. I love you.
来 戴上
Here, put it on.
那么 再说一次我没有发疯 我不应该再考硕士了
So, tell me again I'm not crazy and I shouldn't go get my master's.
不 你应该考的 你应该交些学费去艺术学校
Oh, no, you should. You should go pay some
进修你的绘画
art-school lifer to grade your pictures.
我不用交学费的 我可以用我的奖学金
I don't have to pay them. I can use my grant money.
你说对了
You get the point.
更重要的是 学校在纽约 离我只有3000里远
And more importantly, it's in New York, which is 3,000 miles away from me.
我知道
I know.
我的工作就是赚钱 我向你保证
My job is about to blow up. I promise you.
我们会有钱的 这样就可以开一家你自己的画廊了
I'm gonna have the money so we can open your own gallery.
你可以展示你自己的画
You can shoot your own pictures,
就像我们从前谈论过的
just like we talked about.
- 那不是你想要的吗？- 当然是
- Isn't that what you want? - Of course.
太完美了
This is perfect.
- 嘿 别接电话 行吗？- 嘿 电话在哪儿？
- Hey, don't get that, okay? - Hey. Oh, where is it?
记住我想告诉你一些事
Remember, I wanted to tell you something.
我知道 给我一秒钟
I know. Just give me one second.
是工作上的事 等等
It's work. Hold on.
你好
Hello?
是的
Yeah.
哦 那好
Oh, okay.
好的 不不不 那不… 那不是问题
Right. No no no, it's not... it's not a problem.
好的 再见
All right. Bye-bye.
是布里斯托 我得去上班了
It was Bristol. I have to go to work.
今天是我生日 给他打回去
Yeah, and it's my birthday, so call him back,
告诉他你病了 你不能过去
tell him you're sick. You just can't go.
听着 如果你让我去
Listen. If you do this for me,
明年我们还来这儿
we will come back here next year,
我们整个周末都会呆在这儿
and we will stay the whole weekend,
我们会住在旅馆里 然后…
and we'll get a hotel room, and...
亲爱的？
Baby?
让我过去吧 我真的要去参加这个会
Help me out here. I really need to go to this meeting.
好了 你去吧
No, forget it.
我要一周的时间
I want a week.
- 一周？- 对
- A week? - That's right.
只有你和我没有电话
You and me and no cell phones.
在我们走之前
You can personally
你可以将这个东西弄碎
smash this thing before we leave.
怎么样？
How's that?
好的
Okay.
你知道吗？为什么犹豫？我说…
Actually, you know what? Why wait? I say...
为了保险起见我们 将这个扔到湖里去吧
we just drown this thing now to make sure.
哦 这… 我可不这样认为
Oh! Oh! Oh, that's... I don't think so.
哦 天啊亲爱的 你记得带我的太阳镜了吗？
Aw, shit. Baby, did you remember my sunglasses?
如果没有我你怎么办呢？
Mm? What would you do without me?
真扫兴 布里斯托这个奸细
Yo, this is stupid! Bristol's a dick.
是呀 一个顶替我晋升的奸细
Yeah, a dick who's gonna get promoted instead of me
如果我在这个会议中表现不出色的话
if I flake on this meeting.
- 那么以后他就会毁了我们的星期天了？- 和朱莉的生日
- So he gets to ruin our Sundays then? - And Julie's birthday.
如果我要打败他们 我就得加入他们
If I want to beat 'em, I have to join 'em.
- 现在 - 别
- Right now! - Don't.
无论如何 我告诉你 你应该将整个事情都推掉
Whatever, man. I'm telling you you just should blow the whole thing off.
是呀 你是对的 我不需要这份工作
Yeah, you know, you're right. I don't need this job anyway.
好主意 当你被炒鱿鱼后 我相信
Great idea. And when you get fired I'm sure Trevor will last
没有你 特雷弗也会持续工作两周
about two weeks at work without you.
为什么你非要说这些？
Why do you have to say that?
等一下 等等
Wait, guys. Hold up, hold up.
好了 非常好
Okay. Nice.
亲爱的你知道吗？你可以和我一起搬到纽约去
You know what, baby? You can move to New York with me,
我们可以做一对落魄的艺术家
and we could be starving artists together.
那样岂不是很完美 嗯？
Wouldn't that be perfect, hon?
听起来你将一切都实现了一样
Sounds like you have it all worked out.
糟糕 抓住
Shit! Hold on!
哦 天啊
Oh God!
- 大家没事吧？- 你还好吗？你还好吗？
- Is everyone all right? - You okay? You okay?
- 还好 - 你确定吗？
- I think so. - Are you sure?
- 哦 哦天啊 - 不 糟糕
- Oh! Oh God! - Oh, shit!
尼克 快开
Nick, move! Ah!
《蝴蝶效应2》
尼克
Nick.
Oh, Nick.
尼克 没事的
Nick, it's okay.
9号病房蓝色信号 病人疾病发作
Room 9, we've got a code blue. He's gone into attack.
190 并且继续升高
190 and rising.
尼克
Shh, Nick. Shh.
尼克…
Nick...
没事了
It's okay.
他常常做噩梦
He gets nightmares sometimes.
他总是这样
He always has.
尼克
Nick.
Oh, Nick!
朱莉在哪儿？
Where's Julie?
亲爱的 她已经
Honey, she's...
- 他们呢？- 他们没有
- Where are they? - They didn't...
- 不 不 - 尼克…
- No. No. - Nick...
好了 大家准备好
Okay, everybody.
- 等一下 - 快点儿 快点儿
- Just hold your horses for a minute. - Hurry up, hurry up.
- 来呀 - 不
- Yay! Come on! - No!
你知道吗？现在我无法想象没有你的生活
You know what? I cannot imagine my life without you now.
你知道 我在想 如果你…
You know, I was thinking... if you, um...
如果你需要换换风景什么的
if you really need a change of scenery or whatever,
我这里有多余的房间
I've got some extra room at my place.
为谁准备的？
For what?
你
You.
我想让你和我住在一起
I want you to live with me.
尼克 是妈妈
Nick, it's Mom.
你感觉怎么样了？我同医生谈过了
How you feeling? I spoke to the doctor.
他说你又取消了预约
He said you canceled your appointment again.
尼克 你得学会照顾你自己
Nick, you've got to take care of yourself.
你的头痛病不可以再严重了
You don't want the headaches to get any worse.
请打电话给我
Please, call me.
- 嘿 兄弟 - 什么事？
- Hey, man. - What's up?
- 你病好了吧 - 嗯
- Thought you were out sick. - No.
布里斯托正找你呢 就是没事找事
Bristol's looking for you. Just a heads up.
谢谢
Thanks, man.
- 你不接电话吗？- 当时我在复印室
- You don't pick up your phone? - Oh, I was in the copy room.
我需要这些电子表格
I need those spreadsheets.
昨晚我将他们放到你的桌上了
Yeah, I put 'em on your desk last night.
昨天7点钟我才离开的
I was here until 7:00.
在那之后你检查过你的收件箱吗？
After that. Did you check your inbox?
我告诉你我找不到他们 所以…
Look, I'm telling you I can't find 'em, so just...
你再给我打印一份新的 好弥补一下你无聊的童话故事
print me up a new report, spare me the boring fairy tale.
我们要参加一个罗斯蒙特证券会议 一小时以后
We've got the Rosemont Equities meeting, one hour.
等等 你说什么？
Wait. What are you talking about?
11点 销售说明…
11:00, sales presentation...
- 我以为 4点钟开始 - 我得将它提前 知道吗？
- I thought that was at 4:00. - I had to move it, okay?
那你现在才告诉我？
And you're just telling me this now?
听着 尼克
Look, Nick,
80%的创业者在前两年都是一事无成的 就像走上坡路一样
80% of all start-ups fail in the first two years. It is an uphill battle.
每个人都要把自己的体重加进去 没有例外
Everyone's got to pull their own weight. No exceptions.
好的 没问题 我去拿电子表格
Okay. No problem. I'll have the spreadsheets.
如果你觉得自己不行我可以来办
I can give the pitch myself if you think you can't handle it.
我说了没问题
I said no problem.
好的
Okay.
将你那套收起来
You keep your shit together.
不服气吗？我没功夫顾及你脑子里的狗屁想法 去他妈的
Okay? I can't have you pop another brain fart and fuck this thing up.
将你的桌子收拾干净 这里太乱了
Clean up your desk. It's a mess.
我们在讨论软件 它可以使你的手提电脑
What we're talking about is software that will enable your handheld
与任何无线电科技连接
to communicate with any wireless technology.
想象一下从这里可以 进入到你的所有科技领域中去
Imagine being able to access all of your technology from here.
设想一下 假设你在一辆出租车里 你在赶往会议的途中
Picture it. Say you're in a cab on your way to a meeting.
你正在检查你的邮件 你在网上冲浪 突然来了一个电话
You're checking your e-mails, you're surfing the web, a call comes in.
你的新客户决定他们 需要另外的产品形象设计
Well, your new client decides that they need additional product images
只给你一个小时的时间 在会议中说明他们所需要的东西
to be included in the presentation that you're giving in an hour.
你急忙赶到会议现场
You rush over to the job site
照几张jpeg图片 赶去开会
snap a couple of jpegs, get to your meeting.
先生们 你们拥有的
And gentlemen, what you've got
只是你口袋里的一小块芯片而已
is a slideshow in your pocket.
好的 那么…
Okay, so...
每个人都正在研发 下一代为手提服务的芯片
everyone's developing next-gen software for handhelds,
包括一些大企业
including the big guys.
为什么他们会将钱送到你的腰包里？
Why put money into yours?
因为我们现在就准备好了
Because ours is ready now.
我们与在Strike Line 工作的员工一起 坚信
We, with our partners at Strike Line, believe
不到一个季度我们的 产品就会占领市场
we can have this on the market within the quarter.
- 尼克 - 他有突发疾病什么的吗？
- Nick. - Is he having a seizure or what?
不 他有头痛病尼克 尼克
No, he gets headaches. Nick! Nick!
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我发誓 如果我再收到一份S E C 的通知
I swear, if I get one more S.E.C. notice,
我要将这一堆东西全烧了 然后移居到乔治敦开曼群岛
I'm gonna burn the whole stack and move this thing to the Caymans.
好呀 那里天气也很好
Yeah, the weather's nice there.
这次会议上的事我很抱歉
I'm... sorry about the meeting, sir.
尼克 我本不该告诉你…
Nick, I shouldn't have to tell you...
80%的创业者在前两年都是一事无成的
80% of all start-ups fail within the first two years.
如果我们犯了一个错误 那会影响全局
We make one mistake, it affects everything.
我们不能过回去将事情重来一遍
We can't go back and do this over again.
你说得很对
You're absolutely right.
我向你保证这样的事 决不会再发生了
I assure you this will not happen again.
戴夫告诉我你最近状态不好
Dave tells me you've been having some problems lately
注意力不集中 记忆力减退
with concentrating and remembering stuff.
- 你确定你没事吗？- 我很好
- Are you sure you're okay? - Yeah, I'm fine.
这样 那… 那没什么的
Really, it's... it's not a big deal.
我让你马上回家
I want you to just go home,
休息一周给自己充充电
take the rest of the week off and recharge the batteries.
- 坎拉罕先生 我真的能够工作的 - 尼克…
- Mr. Callahan, really, I can work. - Nick...
我需要工作
I need to work.
就这么决定了 回家吧
It's done. Just go home.
一周后见
We'll see you in a week.
噢
Oh, man.
天啊亲爱的 你拿了我的太阳镜吗？
Oh, shit. Baby, did you grab my sunglasses?
嗯？没有我你该怎么办？
Mm? What would you do without me?
嗯？
Hmm?
真扫兴 布里斯托这个奸细
Yo, this is stupid! Bristol's a dick.
是呀 一个顶替我晋升的奸细
Yeah, a dick who'll get promoted
如果我在这个会议中表现不出色的话
instead of me if I flake on this meeting.
- 那么以后他就会毁了我们的星期天了？- 还有朱莉的生日
- So he gets to ruin our Sundays? - And Julie's birthday.
无论如何 你应该将整个事情都推掉
Whatever, man. I'm telling you you should just blow the whole thing off.
是呀 你知道 你是对的 我不需要这份工作
You're right. I don't really need this job anyway.
好主意
Yeah. Great idea.
当你被炒鱿鱼后 我相信
I'm sure when you get fired, Trevor will last
没有你 特雷弗也会持续工作两周
two weeks at work without you, maybe.
"没有你 特雷弗也会持续工作两周"
"Two weeks at work without you."
- 为什么你非要说这些？- 什么？
- Why you got to say that? - What?
大家等一下 我想照张像
Ooh, guys, wait. I want to get a picture of this.
很好 你知道吗 亲爱的？
Nice. And you know what, honey?
你可以和我一起搬到纽约去
You can move to New York with me and we can be starving artists together.
- 那样岂不是很完美 嗯？- 系好你的安全带
- Isn't that a perfect idea? - Put your seat belt on.
- 什么？- 将安全带系上
- What? - Put it on!
好的 真是的
Okay. Shit.
我还好
I think so.
嘿 亲爱的 你知道要穿哪件吗？
Hey, pumpkin. Hey, do you know what you're gonna wear?
发生什么事了？
What's happening?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
尼克？
Nick?
尼克 你还好吗？
Oh, Nick, are you okay?
你怎么了？
What's wrong, huh? Huh?
怎么了？
What's the matter?
我想我做了个恶梦
I think I was having a nightmare.
哦 亲爱的 没事了
Oh, baby! It's okay.
好了吗？噩梦结束了 结束了
All right? It's all over now. It's all over.
哦 嘘
Oh shh.
哦 天啊
Oh, God!
好了吗？我们出发吧
Okay? Now let's get going.
我们去庆祝我的生日 会很有趣的
We'll celebrate my birthday. It'll be fun.
- 好的 - 我快准备好了
- Okay. - I'm gonna go get ready. All right.
好的
Okay.
我知道这听起来多怪异 只是…
I know how weird it sounds. It's just...
我无法解释 我…
I can't explain it. I...
我的生命居然有另一个版本
there's this entire other version
没有你
of my life without you.
我度过了整整一年没有你的生活
I went through a whole year
我相信你已经不在了
believing you were dead.
之后… 之后我醒来 你出现了
And then I just... I just wake up, and there you are.
好了 那只是个噩梦 好吗？
Okay, it was just a bad dream, all right?
那不是真的
It wasn't real.
我在这 行了
I'm here. Come on.
我听见你说的话了 真的
I hear you, I do,
但是我需要一段时间去相信你回来了
but it's just I'm having a really difficult time believing it.
这一年真的是痛苦不堪
It's been a traumatic year
对我们来说都是 好吗？
for both of us, okay?
- 但是我们挺过去了 - 我说的不是这个
- But we made it. - It's not that.
嘿
Hey.
我在这
I am here.
这才是重要的
And that's all that matters.
好的
All right.
- 好的 - 我就知道
- You're right. - I know.
哦 你说对了
Oh, fuck. You're right.
嘿 抱歉来晚了
Hi. Sorry we're late.
- 生日快乐 - 谢谢
- Happy birthday. - Thank you.
- 25岁生日快乐 老丫头 - 哦
- Happy 25th, old lady. - Oh!
你怎么样 兄弟？
How's it going, man?
很好
Good.
太好了
It is really frickin' good!
真高兴见到你
Oh, it's good to see you, man!
是的 真好
Yeah, it's good. Good.
你们两个 你们看起来好极了
You two, you look amazing!
噢 他喝了多少？
Oh, how much has he had to drink?
是个漫长的夜晚
Well, it's been a long night.
为什么…
Speaking of which, why don't, uh...
- 好的 走… - 你和我一起…
- Yes, let's... - You and I do the...
- 好的 - 好
- Right. - Okay.
你们两个… 好 很好
...and you two... good. All right.
嘿 你近来可好？两杯MGD
Hey, how's it goin', man? Two MGDs,
苏格兰威士忌加冰再来一杯红酒
Jack on the rocks and a house red, please.
告诉我你将脱衣舞女关起来了
Please tell me that you locked down the strippers.
脱衣舞女？
The strippers?
是为我的单身派对准备的
For my bachelor party.
你的单身派对？
Your bachelor party?
因为… 你们两个要结婚了
Because... you two are getting married,
并且 我是… 伴郎
and I'm... the best man.
那就意味着我要将脱衣舞女锁起来
Which means I would have locked down the strippers.
当燃料了 蠢驴
Of course I did, dumb-ass!
- 你别吓唬我 兄弟 - 我找了…
- You're scaring me, man. - Dude, I got the...
10个最性感的舞女
10 hottest strippers ever.
10个？
10?
太好了 谢谢
Awesome! Thanks. Thank you.
我…
I am...
你们真疯狂
I am so psyched for you guys!
哦 好吧
Oh. Okay.
你仍然觉得你在梦中吗？
Do you still think you're dreaming?
宝贝 怎么了？宝贝 怎么了？
Baby, what's wrong? Baby, what's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
- 我爱你 - 我爱你
- I love you. - I love you.
- 哦 天啊 - 好了
- Oh god. - All right, baby.
"在最近的在研究中偏头疼可能引起突发性疾病
"Migraines have been linked to seizures in recent studies.
患病者头痛的频律较高
Patients with a high frequency of migraine attacks
很有可能引起脑中风
are at greater risk for cerebral strokes.
这种进行性脑部疾病可以导致
This progressive brain disease can lead to
急性病导致记忆力丧失
acute and selected memory loss.
行为盖面可能包括…
Behavior changes might include the following...
错觉 幻想 幻听…"
delusions, hallucinations, hearing things that are not actually present..."
"精神分裂症指一种感情与思想上的分裂"
"Schizophrenia refers to a split between emotion and thought."
"研究显示这种疾病具有遗传性
"Studies have shown the disease to be genetically linked,
最后阶段会导致自杀"
which in its end stages can result in suicide."
嘿 感觉怎么样？
Hey! How ya feelin'?
快疯了 还是在看黄色网站
Oh, busted. Looking at porn. Again.
- 是呀 - 顺便说一下
- Yeah. - By the way,
你昨晚真是喝高了
you were really fucked up last night, man.
是呀 我喝了几杯
Yeah, I had a couple of drinks.
- 嗯 几杯 - 呃...
- Yeah, a couple. - Um...
什么？
What?
嘿 伙计们 布里斯托要举行全体会议
Hey, guys. Bristol just called a staff meeting.
5分钟后 会议室
Conference room, five minutes.
哦 天啊那个杂种想要干什么？
Oh, God. What does that prick want now?
我不知道 但他想先见你
I don't know, but he wants to see you in his office beforehand.
什么？哦 你们？
What? Oh. Oh, guys?
我想我已经感觉到了他在踢我的屁股
I think I can already feel his foot up my ass.
好了 我们开始吧
All right, people, let's get right to it.
我已经警告过你们
You've all heard me warn you about the problems
关于一般创业公司所面临的问题
of the average start-up company.
看起来这周我们有亏损
Well, it seems that we've been on the losing end this week.
秋季我们有5笔交易
I had five deals fall through,
包括 R S B 金融公司
including R.S.B. Financial.
那是…
That's...
那是特雷弗的客户 他说过他很有把握
That's Trevor's account. He said it was a sure thing.
他错了
Well, he was wrong.
并且很不幸的是 坎拉罕先生认为
And unfortunately, Mr. Callahan felt
他要发布一个信息
like he had to send a message on this one.
我们不得不解雇特雷弗
We've had to let Trevor go.
那么我建议大家回去工作吧
So I suggest that we all get back to work, hmm?
这是不是太突然了？
Doesn't that seem a little harsh?
是的
Yes.
- 发生什么事了？- 什么？
- So what actually happened? - Excuse me?
哦 如果特雷弗认为
Well, if Trevor thought
这件事已经定了 为什么这笔交易吹了？
it was a sure thing, why'd the deal fall apart?
别开玩笑了 布里斯托
Come on, Bristol.
你曾经做过特雷弗的工作
You had Trevor's job once,
你知道那有多难
and you know how hard it is.
是的 我没命地干活 我没有失误过
Yeah, and I worked my ass off, I didn't make mistakes
我还得了奖励
and I got rewarded.
为什么？因为Strike Line公司的生意
Why? 'Cause the Strike Line deal
落到你们头上了？
fell on your lap?
你应该将与 R S B 的生意结束 而不是特雷弗
You were supposed to close the R.S.B. deal, not Trevor.
你认为你知道些隐秘的事？
And you think you know something we don't?
我所知道的是
What I know
坎拉罕先生付钱 让我评价你们的工作
is Mr. Callahan pays me to be the judge of you people,
现在我对你的评价是
and right now my judgment is telling me that you'd much rather be
你应该坐在家里与朋友们看电视
at home watching "Oprah" with your friend
而不是继续留在这个团队里
than working on this team any longer.
恭喜你 尼克 你也被解雇了
Congratulations, Nick. You're fired too.
还有别人吗？
Anyone else?
兄弟 我爱你 但这不是你的问题
I love you, man, but this was not your problem.
去你的
Fuck that.
如果不是我们 布里斯托根本不能那么快被升职
If it wasn't for us, Bristol wouldn't have been promoted in the first place.
我不是想占他的职位
I'm not taking orders from him.
尼克 你在这地方拼命地工作
Nick, you worked your ass off at this place.
你在这里做牛做马
You put your blood into this place, man.
是呀 我在这里做牛做马 而布里斯托却被升职了
Yeah, I put my blood into this place, and Bristol's the one who gets promoted.
尼克 这就是生意场你教我的
Nick, that's business. You taught me that.
现在 回去跟布里斯托道个歉
Now, look. Go tell Bristol you're sorry.
告诉他你仍然有后遗症
Tell him you're still having side effects from the accident.
我唯一的后遗症是明白了人生太仓促
Only side effect I'm having is knowing life is way too short for this.
这是什么 男人的专利？
What is this, a guy thing?
特雷弗被冻结账户了 那么你就和他一起跳？
Trevor gets canned, so you just jump off the bridge with him?
听着 我从未想到过要提升布里斯托
Look, I was never gonna move up with Bristol as my supervisor anyway.
自从那家伙被晋升了
Ever since the guy got promoted,
他一直在找借口解雇我
he's just been looking for an excuse to fire me.
- 那你就不要给他机会 - 你知道吗？事实上
- Well, you didn't have to give him one. - You know what? The truth is,
他才是个薄弱环节 是他毁了整个公司
he's the weak link. He's ruined the whole company,
每个人都知道 你知道吗？
and everybody knows it. And you know what?
从他的管治下脱离出来才是上策
I am better off just getting out from under him.
不 尼克 你最好要回你的工作
No, Nick. You're better off with a job.
我告诉过你 我会去找另一份工作
I told you, I'll find another one.
一个更好的 我们会过得很好
A better one. We'll all be okay.
你同样说过你会呆在 这儿而不去纽约 因为那样也行得通
You also told me to stay here and not go to New York, because that would be okay.
很抱歉
I'm sorry,
我只是不能忘记在 那次事故中我们所失去的
and I just can't forget what we lost in that accident.
嗯？
Hon?
嘿
Hey.
嘿 一切会好的
Hey, it will be.
只是需要时间
It just takes time.
尼克 已经一年了
Nick, it's been a year.
我每天靠计算别人的照片为生 却只赚一点点钱
I spend my days cataloguing other people's photo shoots for minimum wage.
我有半个文件夹的东西要看 但我没有时间完成 现在…
I have half a portfolio and no time to finish it, and now...
现在我得去找另一份工作这样我们可以付租金
Well, now I have to get another job so that we can pay our rent.
不好意思
Excuse me.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
嘿
Hey.
这有关于我们的未来 我现在总算可以看到了
It's about the big picture. I finally see it now.
所有的一切杂事… 只是杂事
All that other stuff is just... just stuff.
听着 唯一重要的是
Look, the only thing that is important
我们拥有彼此
is that we have each other.
这才是重点
That's all that counts.
你总是像推销员一样 不是吗？
Always the salesman, aren't you?
嗯 也许我会成为一个技术复印编辑
Mm. Maybe I'll be a technical copyeditor.
那是布里斯托？混蛋
Is that Bristol? Jerk.
来吧
Come on.
尼克？
Nick?
尼克
Nick.
- 完美的照片 - 太好了
- Perfect shot. - Ah! Great.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
- 照得不错吧？- 你看上去很棒
- Isn't that great? - You look so good.
真好 你觉得怎么样？
Nice. So, what do you think?
- 嗯？- 这戒指 亲爱的 很漂亮不是吗？
- Hmm? - The ring, honey. Isn't it beautiful?
你相信是我自己选的吗？
Can you believe I picked that thing out myself?
- 太美了 - 哦
- It's fantastic. - Ooh.
嗯 是呀 很漂亮
Yeah. Sure, it's beautiful.
我们正在考虑明年十月
We're thinking next October.
你们打算请多少人？
Oh, how many people are you gonna invite?
也许50个 只有重要的一些人
You know, maybe 50. Just the important ones.
- 嗯 - 对
- Mmm. - Ah. Right.
- 戴夫 布里斯托 - 什么？
- Dave Bristol. - What?
你的同事吗？
From your office?
是的 像是我发明的这个工具
Yeah, right. Like I'd invite that tool.
我喝完了 还有人需要吗？
Looks like I'm out. Anyone else need more?
噢 不了 亲爱的
Oh, no, honey.
布里斯托 圣诞节快乐
Bristol, merry Christmas.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
你在干什么？尼克
Oh, come on, Nick!
- 你在干什么？- 布里斯托 对不起
- What are you doing? - Bristol, I'm sorry, man.
真糟糕 我可以…
What a klutz. Can I...
好啊真是好
Nice. That's really nice.
哦 天啊
Oh, man.
真尴尬
Oh, that's embarrassing,
so embarrassing.
不可以
No way.
嘿 尼克
Hey, Nick.
我知道你需要这些电子表格
I know you need those spreadsheets.
我只是在等一些客户的数据
I'm just waiting on some numbers from the clients.
操
Holy shit.
我是副总裁
I'm the vice president.
哦 当然 我没有在找借口
Uh, yeah, of course. I'm not trying to make excuses.
是我搞定了Strike Line 公司的合同 不是你
I pulled the Strike Line deal, not you.
对不起 我没听明白
I'm sorry. I'm just not following this.
特雷弗在哪儿
Where's Trevor?
在外面跟客户见面 他说你知道的
At some off-site client meeting. He said you knew about it.
哦 没错 谢谢
Oh, yeah, right. Thanks.
对了 还有 布里斯托 把桌子收拾一下 乱七八糟的
Oh, and Bristol, clean up that desk. It's a mess.
我发誓 如果我再收到 一次证监会的通告
I swear, if I get one more S.E.C. notice,
我就把这堆东西烧了 然后送到南美鳄鱼那儿
I am gonna burn the whole stack and move this thing to the Caymans.
我听说那里天气不错
Well, I hear the weather's nice there.
好像是吧 你感觉如何
Yeah, I guess. So how you feelin'?
再好不过了
Oh, better than ever.
听着 我要和一个准客户吃晚饭
Listen, I'm having dinner with a potential investor.
他可是个大客户 我们需要他
He's a big one. We need him.
你知道 好的开始是成功的一半
You know what they say about start-ups.
我要你全副武装上阵
I want you riding shotgun.
我不会搞砸的 卡里恩先生
I wouldn't miss it for the world, Mr. Callahan.
"卡里恩先生" 叫得真可爱
"Mr. Callahan." That's cute.
"太平洋街"
"Pacific Avenue."
这里是朱莉米勒摄影社
You've reached Julie Miller Photography.
我无法接电话 所以请留言
I can't take your call, so please leave a message,
包括您的电话号码 和您想预约的日期
including your phone number and the date you'd like to book.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好 朱莉米勒摄影社
Well, hello there, Julie Miller Photography.
我是尼克拉森
It's Nick Larson calling,
我想和你预约在今晚与客户见面后
and the date I would like to book is for tonight after my client meeting,
但愿见客户不会花太长时间
which hopefully won't last too long.
所以为何不给我回个电话
So why don't you give me a call back
告诉我你有没有空
and let me know if that works for your schedule?
当然了 除非我会在家先见到你 好了 我爱你 宝贝
Unless of course I see you at home first. All right. I love you, babe.
亲爱的 我到家啦
Honey, I'm home!
不会吧
No.
什么
What?
嘿 尼克 我是妈妈 我希望你还好
Hey, Nick, it's Mom. I hope you're okay.
我的确好极了
I'd say so.
给我回电话 都几个星期没见了 我知道你很忙
Call me. I haven't seen you for weeks. I know you're busy,
但是得让我知道你过得怎样啊
but let me know how you are.
为合作成功干杯
A toast... to successful partnerships.
- 干杯 - 干杯
- Salud. - Salud.
你女儿长得又迷人又漂亮
Your daughter is charming and beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯 那你呢 尼克？
Mm. And what about you, Nick?
你在这儿有亲人吗？
Do you have family here?
只有我妈
Uh, just my mom. Yeah.
我爸在我小时候就离开了
My, uh... my father moved away when I was a kid.
很遗憾听你这么说
Ah. I am very sorry to hear that.
看上去你过得还挺好的
Well, it seems that you turned out all right.
你可是给你老板添光了
You have certainly made an impression on your boss.
呵呵
Oh, well...
尼克最近多了点儿第六感
Nick's had a bit of a magic touch lately.
我只不过是尽量把事情简化
Well, I just try to keep things simple, you know?
找到目标 然后尽力实现
Know what you want and try to make that happen.
如果这还不行的话 就从旁边的人手里
And if that doesn't work out, you steal the file
把东西偷过来 然后盼着那个人是赢家
from the guy sitting next to you and hope that one's a winner.
好吧 尼克 让我来谈点正事儿
All right, Nick. Well, let's get serious for a minute
把这些新数据告诉弗恩逖司先生
and tell Mr. Fuentes about the new numbers.
现在吗？我们正谈得开心呢
Now? Oh, we're having such a good time.
新数据 尼克
The new numbers, Nick.
我们正在管弗恩逖司先生要一大笔投资
We're about to ask Mr. Fuentes for a large amount of money.
你得从他口袋里把钱包弄到手
You have to dazzle the wallet out of his pocket
然后让它在桌上跳舞
and make it dance on the table.
不了 真的 瑞安 还是由你来说吧 这是你的心血
No, really, Ron, you take the glory. This is your baby.
数据 尼克
The numbers, Nick.
我们真正谈论的
Well, what we're, uh... we're really talking about
是 嗯
is, uh...
新一代掌上操作系统
the next generation of hand-held operating systems.
我们的软件基于因特网光传输协议
Our software capitalizes on optical internet protocol,
使用光波结构处理
using light-wave architectures for processing
所以它将在多重波长下收发数据
so that it will send and receive data over multiple wavelengths.
我们的系统可以在6个月内商业化
Our system can be commercialized within six months,
并且有了可用测试版本 以及贵公司的支持
and with a working beta product and your company's backing,
我们预期 可以在负责人中 签定一个甚至两个
we can expect to sign one, maybe two of the incumbents.
这样我们就能从中国生产商外购
Then we'll minimize our front-end expenditures
从而最小化整个过程的支出
by outsourcing to a flex manufacturer in China.
如果一切顺利的话 我们产品的边际效益就会
If we're right, our product margins will add
在12个月内 为贵公司 的毛利增加500个基本点
500 basis points to your company's gross margins within 12 months.
底线是 如果我们达到 预期销售额的三分之一
Bottom line, if we achieve one-third of the unit sales forecasted,
就能使贵公司的现金流量翻倍
we'll double your company's cash flow.
好了
All right.
嘿 怎么样了
Hey. How's it going?
我正想拉直我的头发 我太无聊了
I'm about to pull out my hair, I'm so bored.
是啊这个
Yeah, it's, uh...
对不起 关于所有无聊的技术性描述
sorry for all the technobabble.
实际上 你知道吗 那才是让我兴奋的部分
Actually, you know, that's the part that got me hot.
格雷斯？
Grace?
哦 上帝
Oh Jesus.
你在干吗？
What are you doing?
宝贝 已经一个星期了
Baby, it's been a week.
难道你要我求你吗？
What, you want me to beg for it?
嘿 我们可是在饭店里呢
Whoa. Hey. Hey hey hey. We're in a restaurant.
这个什么时候又能阻止你？
When has that ever stopped you before?
哦 我操
Oh fuck.
停一下 你爸就在外面
Hold up. Your dad's right outside.
我可不在乎这个 他也不在乎
I don't care about that, and neither does he.
再说了 大不了我再让他给你升职
Besides, I'll just tell him to give you another raise.
哦 尼克
Oh, Nick!
- 我要你 - 听到了
- I want you, Nick. - I hear you.
耶
Yeah.
Yeah!
哦 我的上帝 你在干吗？
Oh my God. What are you doing?
让我们玩儿点有意思的
Let's have some fun here.
笑一个 宝贝
Smile, baby.
嘿
Uh-uh. Hey...
- 我会再联系你的 - 你永远最受欢迎
- I'll be in touch. - You're most welcome.
你做的很好 尼克 谢谢你能来
You did great, Nick. Thanks for coming.
是啊尼克 感谢你过来
Yeah, Nick. Thanks for coming.
- 哦 上帝 - 你去哪儿了
- Oh! Jesus! - Where were you?
我都等了2个小时了
I was waiting for two hours.
特雷弗 冷静 伙计 我和卡林去吃晚餐了
Trevor, settle down, man. I was at dinner with Callahan.
什么 我告诉过你 我们需要谈谈
What? I told you, we need to talk.
好吧 到底怎么回事？
All right. What's going on?
我和我的一个投资人出了问题
I've got a problem with one of my investors.
- 谁？- 马尔科姆
- Who? - Malcolm.
- "马尔科姆"？- 你在耍我吗？
- "Malcolm"? - Are you playing with me?
马尔科姆 俱乐部认识的 我们拿了他的钱 你谈好的合同
Malcolm, from the club. We took his money. You closed the deal.
- 你脑袋有毛病了？醒醒 - 马尔科姆 没错
- Is your head fucked? Come on! - Malcolm, of course.
对 怎么了？发生什么了？
Yes. What's up? What's going on?
那钱 他想要回他的钱
The money... h-he-he... he wants it back.
- 好吧 多少钱？- 所有的
- All right. How much? - All of it.
- 25万 - "25万"？
- 250 grand. - "250 grand"?
- 是他打的你吗？- 是他的手下 当是个提醒
- Did he do that to you? - It was one of his guys, as a reminder.
听着 听我说 尼克
Just listen. Listen to me, Nick.
你得弄到这笔钱 伙计 好吗？
You've got to make this happen, man, okay?
因为我无法糊弄这个家伙
'Cause I can't mess around with this guy.
我 我不敢让他再等了
I...I...I can't make him wait anymore.
嘿 特雷弗
Hey, Trevor...
让我跟瑞安谈谈 我会搞定这件事的
I'll talk to Ron. I'll take care of it.
没什么大不了的 好吗？
It's no big deal. All right?
- 对 对 好吧 - 好的
- Yeah. Yeah, all right. - All right, okay.
- 我欠你一辈子 兄弟 - 不 伙计
- I owe you my life, man. - No no. Dude.
- 没事儿的 - 好吧
- It's all right. - All right.
嘿
Hey.
你最近和朱莉说过话吗
You, uh... you talk to Julie lately?
没 有一阵没说过话了 怎么了？
No. Not in a while. Why?
我一直找不到她
I'm having a hard time tracking her down.
兄弟
Dude.
上次你告诉我 你俩分手了 是吧？
You told me last time, you're done with her, right?
再见
See you later.
瑞安 怎么样了？
Ron. How's it going, man?
糟透了 弗恩逖司的生意丢了
For shit. Fuentes bailed.
什么？你不是开玩笑吧
What? You got to be kidding me.
昨晚过后 我还以为我们搞定他了呢
After last night I thought we had him.
是啊操他妈的 他的错
Yeah, well, fuck him. His mistake.
哦 上帝
Oh, Jesus!
听着 我不想火上浇油 但是
Listen, I hate to pile on, man, but, um,
看起来我们的一个投资人出现问题了
it seems we have a problem with one of our investors.
- 哦 是吗？- 是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
盖伊特雷弗7月份带进来的 给我们投资了25万？
Guy Trevor brought in back in July, gave us 250 grand?
总之 他说他想把钱要回来
Anyway, he says, uh... he says he wants it back.
- 就这样？- 是的
- That's it? - Yeah.
那不过是点儿零花钱
That's pocket change.
为何你不去把我桌上的 支票本拿来 自己写上钱数？
Why don't you just go get the checkbook off my desk and write it yourself?
瑞安 太感谢你了 伙计 我就知道你会理解的
Ron, thank you so much, man. I knew you'd understand.
为何不在我桌上也写点别的？
Why don't you write a few more while you're at it?
我是说 不如你到那儿去 用牛奶和饼干把他们吓晕好了
I mean, just go down to the corner and pass 'em out with milk and cookies.
如果你真的要送出些钱的话
I mean, if you really want to give some money away.
不是这样的 伙计
It's not like that, man.
尼克 我们有合同
Nick, we have contracts
上面写的有何时 何种情况才能拿到钱
that specify how and when people get paid back.
我知道 我也能理解 但是 以后不会再发生这种事儿了
I know. I understand. Look, it is a one-time thing.
下次做生意时我会给你补上的
I'll make it up to you on the next deal.
我不明白 昨天我们 谈话时你一直在睡觉吗？
I don't get it. Were you asleep for our entire conversation yesterday?
哪次谈话？
Which... which one?
我告诉你我们破产了的那次
The one where I told you we're broke.
- 什么？- 尼克 我们没钱了
- What? - Nick, the money is gone.
无论再怎么说 我们还是没钱
No matter how many times we go over it, it is gone.
我们花的比我们赚的还要多
We've spent it... everything we had and more.
- 瑞安 这不可能 - 你不这么想罢了
- Ron, that's not possible. - You wouldn't think so,
但是由于某些因素 我们曾试着摆脱困境
but somehow we managed to pull it off.
那次Strike Line公司的交易呢？
What about the Strike Line deal?
尼克 你是个优秀的推销员
Nick, you're a good salesman.
你为我的公司做了很多贡献
You've done a lot of great things for my company.
我很高兴把你提拔成副总
I'm glad I made you V.P.,
但还是让我们面对现实吧 那个生意你搞砸了
but let's face it... you blew it on that one.
你在说什么啊？
What are you talking about?
你在圣诞节期间跟他们谈生意
You approached them during Christmas.
那时我们还没准备好
We weren't ready.
无论你怎么想 尼克 你把他们给吓跑了 这是事实
No matter how you look at it, Nick, you scared them off. That's the truth.
Strike Line的生意不是我做的啊
I didn't make the Strike Line deal.
妈的 如果我们能把那个生意给盯死
Hell, you know, if... if we had just nailed that deal,
我们手上就很可能有些能用的软件
we'd actually probably have some working software right now
而不是现在这堆垃圾
instead of this pile of garbage.
嘿
Hey.
- 干得怎么样了？- 还在想办法
- So what's the story? - Still working on it.
尼克 快点 我今晚就要见马尔科姆了
Nick, come on, man. I'm meeting Malcolm tonight.
嘿 我会搞定的
Hey. I'm gonna take care of it.
好的
Okay.
喂 朱莉
Julie. Hey, it's, uh...
嘿 是我 尼克
it's me, Nick, again.
听着 我知道我们之间有些问题
listen, I know that there's some stuff between us,
而显然你不给我回电话 但是
and you're obviously not calling me back, but...
我真的很想和你谈谈
I'd really like to talk to you.
给你迟到的生日祝福 还有
Happy belated birthday, and, uh...
我想你
I miss you.
- 喂？- 尼克 终于打通了
- Hello? - Nick. Finally.
- 哦 你好 妈妈 - 你还好吗？
- Oh, hey, Mom. - How are you?
还好 什么事？
Fine, uh, what's up?
我和你爸的医生谈过了 他想见见你
I've spoken to your father's doctor. He'd like to see you.
你愿意和他说话吗？
Will you talk to him?
为什么？这是什么意思？
Why? What... what do you mean?
我很担心你 我真的很想来看看你
I'm concerned about you. I really want to come and see you.
- 不 妈妈 我很好 - 不是的 我真的很想
- No no, I'm good, Mom. I'm fine. - No, I really...
嘿 我得走了 好吗 我会再打给你的
Hey, listen, I got to go, okay? I'll call you later.
- 尼克 - 我爱你
- Nick... - I love you.
再见
Bye.
让我看看 哦 看上去不错啊
Let me see. Oh, looks good, huh?
朱莉
Julie.
嘿
Hey.
哇 我
Wow, I...
差点没认出你来 你看上去变了好多
hardly recognized you, you look so different.
嗯 谢谢 我想
Uh, thanks, I think.
不 我是说 你看上去很漂亮
No, I mean, you look beautiful.
我给你留了一大堆留言 你收到了吗？
Um, I left you a bunch of messages. Did you get 'em?
是的 我收到了
Yeah, I got 'em.
好吧
Okay.
对不起 我知道我…
I'm sorry. I know I...
我有点儿失礼了 我只想和你谈谈
I got a little carried away. I just really wanted to talk to you.
我就站在这儿 谈吧
Well, I'm standing here, so go ahead.
你在做什么呢？
Um... What are you doing?
- 我在工作 - 在酒吧？
- I'm working. - At a club?
是的 在夜总会 我正在为时装秀拍照
Yeah, at a club. I'm shooting a fashion show.
嗯 不错 谁介绍的？
Well, that's cool. Who hooked that up?
克里斯多佛 他把我介绍给几个人 然后就这么定了
Christopher. He introduced me to a few people and it just took off.
谁是克里斯多佛
Wow. Who's Christopher?
- 嘿 宝贝 - 嘿
- Hey, baby. - Hey.
- 你给我打电话了？- 是的
- You call me? - I did.
- 这又是谁？- 哦 尼克
- And who's this? - Oh, uh, Nick.
老朋友 我们正谈着呢
Old friend. We're just catching up.
尼克 她是最棒的 不是吗 她会成为明星的 对吧 宝贝
Nick, she's the greatest, isn't she? She's gonna be a star, aren't you, baby?
听着 我要再去喝杯酒
Listen, I'm gonna get another drink.
- 我用给你带点儿什么吗？- 好啊
- Can I get you something? - Sure.
- 尼克 你呢？- 不用了 我很好
- Nick? - No, I'm good.
好的
All right
朱莉 朱莉
Julie. Julie.
听着
Listen,
我知道我们之间有些问题
I know some stuff went wrong with us,
但你要相信我 我从没有想过这样分手
but you have to believe me, I never meant for it to end up like this.
哦 别说废话了 尼克 你知道吗？
Oh, cut the shit, Nick. You know what?
你得到了所有你想要的
You got everything exactly the way you wanted it,
所以别又从现在开始关心我了
so don't start caring about me now.
告诉你 无论我说了什么
I am telling you, whatever I said,
做了什么 无论我俩之间发生了什么
whatever I did, whatever... happened between us,
都从你脑海里忘掉吧
just... just wipe it out of your head.
你还不明白吗？我已经都忘了
Don't you get it? I already have.
知道吗 你一直在说你的工作
You know, and all your talk about your job
和我的职业 我们的未来
and my career, the future,
那只是 尼克 说说而已
that's all it was, Nick... talk.
但是现在 我自己做老板了
And now I'm my own boss,
并且第一次按照自己的想法去做
and for the first time I'm doing exactly what I want to do.
不 你没有
No, you're not.
我知道你想要什么 不是这样的
I know what you want, and it's not this.
- 人是会变的 - 我们没变
- Things change. - Not us.
朱莉 我们可以重新开始
Julie, we can start over.
就给我个机会吧
Just give me a chance.
- 她的电话 不是吗？- 谁的？
- That's her, isn't it? - Who?
格雷斯
Grace.
朱莉 不是的
Julie, no.
你是这世界上我唯一关心的
You are the only thing in this world that matters to me.
我不知道为何我曾迷失
I don't know how I lost sight of that.
但我能恢复过来
I can fix this.
我向你保证 我会的
I promise you I will.
不愧是个推销员 不是吗？
Always the salesman, aren't you?
嘿
Hey...
尼克 哦 感谢上帝
Nick. Oh, thank God.
看 我跟你说他会来的
See, I told you he'd show.
我很高兴你能来 尼克
I'm really glad you could make it, Nick.
- 我猜你就是马尔科姆 - 是的
- Malcolm, I assume. - Yeah,
- 很高兴终于面对面见到你 - 我也是
- good to meet you face to face finally. - And you.
这是韦恩 他是我合伙人 拥有夜总会的一半股份
This is Wayne. He owns half the club with me.
韦恩？尼克
Wayne? Nick.
祝你好运
Good luck.
坐吧
Have a seat.
好的
All right.
马尔科姆 这个地方真棒
Malcolm, this space is fantastic.
多谢了
Thank you very much.
请尝尝 一些红茶
Here we go. A little black tea
加上人参和芒果
with ginseng and mango.
我们管它叫中国火箭燃料
We call it Chinese rocket fuel.
使你头脑和身体保持清醒
Keeps you sharp, mind and body.
看起来对你很有效啊
It seems to be working for you.
我知道你为什么会来这儿
I know why you're here.
你想重新谈谈你的合同
You want to renegotiate your contract.
没错
Yes.
你的朋友做了很多承诺
Your friend made a lot of promises.
他说能让我凭着某种 涡轮增压般的超级电话软件
Said he could get me in on the ground floor, triple my money with some sort of
站着就让我的钱翻成3倍
turbocharged super-phone software,
我不是专业人士但这听起来很好
and I'm no expert, but it sounded pretty good.
确实是很好 马尔科姆
And it is, Malcolm.
这都是真的
That's all true.
这是个非常好的软件 我确信你的投资能得到超值回报
It is an excellent product. I'm sure your investment will see a great return.
马尔科姆 我不知道 什么才是你想要的
Malcolm, I'm not sure what it is you're looking for,
但如果你看看合同 就会发现 我们离合同期限还早着呢
but if you look at your contract, you'll see we're well within our timeline.
好吧 但是有时候
Okay, but at some time,
我需要感觉到事情正在进展中
I need to feel like there's some sort of progress going on.
那好 我该怎样帮你有这种感觉呢？
Okay. Well, how can I help you feel like that?
你看 我们是机构的一部分
See, we're part of an organization.
一系列命令的运作总得有个过程 这就是生意如何运作的
There's a chain of command. It's the way things are done.
这就是为什么在合同上注明了
Which is why we sign contracts that specify
何时何种情况下才能得到收益
how and when people are paid back.
你是个商人 你知道整个生意是怎么进行的
You're a businessman. You know how the whole thing works.
你曾希望能预知未来吗？
Have you ever wished you could look into the future?
中国人相信 通过茶叶的形态 就能预测未来
The Chinese believe it's possible just by looking at a pattern of tea leaves.
所以 现在的问题是
So... the question is,
我是看到你们所说的
do I see a waterfall
瀑布般从天而降的钞票
dripping with all the money you guys are gonna make me?
看到我给你们的钱都在
Do I see a little bonfire cooking as everything
- 篝火的烟雾中消失 - 不是这样的 马尔科姆
- I gave you goes up in smoke? - That's not it, Malcolm.
你要能证明给我看的话就好了
Well, I'm dying for you to prove me otherwise.
我觉得我可以
I think I can help.
由于你和特雷弗的关系
Because of your relationship with Trevor
还有我对产品的信心
and my confidence in this product,
我写了张投资钱数10%的个人支票
I've written you a personal check for 10%.
25万中的2万5？
25 thousand out of 250?
这不过是你的投资
It's a Band-Aid until your...
得到回报前的一点儿零头
your investment sees its return.
一点儿零头 我喜欢一点儿零头
Band-Aids. I love Band-Aids.
现在你看到了吧 我告诉过你
Now, you see? I told you,
尼克正在做这笔生意 他会把一切都管好的
Nick's on this now, and he's gonna take care of everything.
有一点儿总比没有强
Well, it's better than nothing,
这就是目前我能拿到的
which is all I've gotten from you so far.
所以 也许现在该废话少说了 对吗？
So, maybe it's time we cut out the middlemen, right?
不
No!
把他弄出去
Get him out.
尼克？
Nick?
- 不要 - 什么？
- No! - What?
在这儿等着 好吗？
Stay in here, okay?
快点 让让 快出去
Come on, move, move! Get out!
妈的 快出去 现在
Shit! Get out! Now!
操
Fuck! Fuck!
朱莉？
Julie?
- 尼克？- 不
- Nick? - No!
朱莉 不要 我操
No, Julie! Fuck!
- 哦 朱莉 哦 上帝 - 发生什么了？
- Oh, Julie! Oh, my God! - What's happening?
嘘 我爱你 宝贝
Shh. Shh. I love you, baby.
我爱你 你还好 好吗？
I love you. You're okay, okay?
这儿 别回头 嘿 看着我
Here. Don't look. Here here. Hey, look at me.
看着我 一切都好 知道吗？
Look at me, look at me. Everything's fine. Okay?
你不会有事儿的 嘘
You're okay. Shh.
快呼吸
Breathe.
别这样啊
Come on!
呼吸 快呼吸
Breathe. Just breathe.
好吧
All right. All right.
哦 格雷斯
Oh, Grace!
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
终于发现怎样能把你弄醒了
Found something that would wake you up.
这他妈的怎么回事儿？
What the fuck?
放松点儿 你正在享受呢
Relax. You're enjoying it.
你的衣服在地上
Your shit's on the floor.
想喝点儿什么吗？
You want something to drink?
你是谁？
Who are you?
我怎么到这儿的？
How did I get here?
你真他妈可爱
You are so bloody cute.
- 回答我的问题 - 把你的手从我身上拿开
- Answer the question. - Get your hands off of me.
你不记得我了？我们在夜总会见过面
You don't remember me? We met at the club.
我和马尔科姆 无论什么事情上
Malcolm and I are partners.
都是合伙人 这就意味着 我也拥有你的一半
On everything. Which means I own half your ass.
我知道你欠我们25万
I understand you owe us $250,000.
如果你表现好的话
If you hadda behaved yourself,
我可以说服马尔科姆管你少要点儿
I could've persuaded Malcolm into reducing your bill,
但在他来之前 你哪儿也不能去
but now you're not going anywhere until he gets here.
听明白没？
Don't you get it?
你要找死的话 我相信 特雷弗和你女朋友都会同意的
I'm sure your girlfriend and Trevor would agree.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
我真把事情给搞砸了 妈妈
I really screwed things up, Mom.
我如此努力去挽救一切
I tried so hard to fix everything, to just...
要把事情做好 但每次 却把事情变得更坏
make things right, and every time I do I make it so much worse.
我甚至都不再知道自己是谁了
I don't even know who I am anymore.
别这样 你说话的样子 让我想起了你爸
Don't. You remind me of your father when you talk like that.
- 为什么？- 你总想掌控一切
- Why? - You try to control everything.
妈妈 我想和爸爸谈谈
Mom, I want to talk to Dad.
不 你不能 好吗？
No, you can... you can't, okay?
你不明白 这真的很重要
You don't understand. It's really important.
- 不 你不明白 - 妈妈 你得帮我找到他
- No, you don't understand. - Mom, you've gotta help me find him.
尼克 他死了
Nick, he's dead.
他自杀了
He committed suicide.
你为什么之前不告诉我？
Why would you keep that from me?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不想让你在这种情况下记住他
I didn't want you to remember him like that.
问题是 尼克 你才是我所担心的
The point is, Nick, it's you I'm worried about.
你独自承受不了
You can't do this alone.
你要去找个医生看看
You need to see a doctor.
你不一定非得和你爸的命运一样
You don't have to have the same fate as your father.
尼克 你无法掌控一切
Nick, you can't control everything.
是时候放手了
You have to let it go.
请再来一杯
Another drink, please.
谢谢
Thanks.
尼克 怎么回事儿？
Nick. What's going on?
哦 上帝
Oh my God.
你发生什么了？
What happened to you?
带来了吗？
Did you bring it?
特雷弗在哪儿？
Where is Trevor?
我都不敢相信这是一年前的
I can't believe that was only a year ago.
我知道有些地方不对劲儿
I know something's wrong.
先是特雷弗带着黑眼眶回家
First, Trevor comes home with a black eye.
然后他说你们要开些会
Then he says you have some meeting together,
但他根本就不回家
but he doesn't come home at all.
现在你又让我带些旧照片过来
And now you want me to bring you some old picture?
尼克 我真的很害怕
Nick, I'm really scared.
我知道
I know.
你知道我愿意为特雷弗 做任何事情 对吧？
You know that I'd do anything for Trevor, don't you?
我愿为你们做任何事情
I'd do anything for all you guys.
是的
Yeah.
过来
Come here.
我知道你很害怕
I know you're scared.
我可以解释的
I can't explain it...
但我向你保证特雷弗没事儿
but I promise you that Trevor's okay.
哦 好极了 伙计们
Oh, great, guys.
看好了
Check it out...
我带来了我特制的生日蜡烛
I brought my own special birthday candle.
- 好啊 - 这可是毒品
- Yes! - It's drugs!
哦 我的最爱
Oh! My favorite.
点蜡烛
Light it!
- 点蜡烛 - 好的 好的
- Light it. - Yes yes.
你去哪儿？
Where are you going?
- 随便转转 - 哦 真的吗？
- Somewhere. - Oh, really?
和你一起
With you.
好吧
Okay.
我要单独和你谈谈
I need to talk to you alone.
穿上这个 天气可能会变冷
Put this on, it might get cold.
啊这里就跟你第一次带我来时
Ah. This looks exactly the same as it did
看上去一摸一样
when you first brought me here.
简直不敢相信 那是什么时候？
I can't believe... when was that?
- 3年前 - 3年前
- Three years ago. - Three years ago.
现在 我无法想象 没有你我的人生会怎样
I can't imagine my life without you now.
尼克 我想跟你说点事儿
Nick, I want to tell you something.
我先说
Me first.
好的
Okay.
你得去纽约
You need to go to New York.
- 什么？- 我知道这听起来很奇怪
- What? - I know that it sounds strange,
但是请相信我 这是为你好
but trust me, it's for the best.
这都哪儿跟哪儿啊？
Where is this coming from?
这是你追求艺术
This is your chance to pursue your art,
发现自我的机会
to... find out about yourself,
不必再为我 为我们 为我的工作
to not have to worry about me or us or my job
或其它的事情担忧
or all that other bullshit, just...
- 我不想这么自由 - 听我说
- I don't want to be free. - Listen to me.
这是你最后一次
This is your last chance to...
可以追求自己生活轨迹
pursue your own path in life,
又不会被我破坏的机会
one that I can't fuck up.
我不想追求自己的生活轨迹 不是那么回事儿
Well, I don't want to pursue my own path. That wasn't the deal.
- 听着 - 我们可以在一起的
- Listen. - We were going to do this together
可以一起解决问题 并且你答应过我 会和我在一起
and we were gonna work it out, and you promised you would be there.
相信我吧 我知道 宝贝 你没明白
Just trust me, I know, baby. I don't think you're getting it.
朱莉
Julie...
我只是现在需要一点私人空间
I just need a little space myself right now.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你要和我分手吗？
You're breaking up with me?
- 就这样了？- 是的
- That's it? - Yeah.
我觉得没什么好说的了
I don't think there's anything left to be said.
尼克 我怀孕了
Nick, I'm pregnant.
特雷弗
Trevor.
朱莉在哪儿？
Where's Julie?
- 发生什么事儿了？- 伙计 她跑下来
- What happened? - Yeah, dude, she ran down here,
拿了你的钥匙 然后开走了你的车
grabbed your keys and took off to your car.
不 哦 上帝
No! Oh God!
- 好吧 我们开始 - 继续走到点上然后回来
- All right, here we go. - Keep going to the point and back.
嘿 伙计 你在干吗？这是我的车
Hey, man, what are you doing? That's my car!
慢点儿 求你了 慢点儿
Slow down. Please, slow down.
哦 上帝
Oh God.
- 哦 真是开玩笑 - 朱莉
- Oh, you've got to be kidding. - Julie!
- 上帝 - 停车 朱莉 求求你了
- God! - Pull over, Julie, please!
求你了 快停车
Please, pull over.
对不起 我爱你
I'm sorry! I love you!
我不知道 对不起
I didn't know! I'm sorry!
朱莉 你一定得停车
Julie, you have to pull over!
停车 你不理解
Pull over! You don't understand!
求你了
Please!
哦 我的上帝
Oh my God.
我爱你
I love you.
我愿为你们做任何事情
I would do anything for all you guys.
你知道的 对吧？
You know that, don't you?
嘿 尼克 你醒了
Hey, Nick. You're awake.
快点 宝贝 今天可是很重要啊
Come on, baby, we've got a big day.
半小时候后我还有课
I've got class in a half-hour.
这就对了 小尼克
That's right, Nicky, yeah!
妈妈半小时内要赶到课堂
Mommy has to go to class in a half an hour.
这就对了 好吧？
That's right. Okay?
我会把你放到奶奶家
I'm gonna drop you off at Grandma's. Yeah!